http://shareyourwallpapers.com/privacy/

Categories3d And Digital ArtAnimalsAnimeCarsCartoonsCelebrities FemaleCelebrities MaleComic BooksComputerCountriesGamesHolidaysMoviesMusicNaturePeoplePhoto ArtSportsTV SerialsVehiclesNewestBuickAdriana SephoraMarianna MerkulovaBecky RobertsRachel MayVinna ReedThaís PazetoGracieSensual JaneAmia MileyAbella DangerGingerMarga & CelesteCarlotta ChampagneCapriceAni Black FoxAmber AAbby Lee
Privacy PolicyHome « Privacy PolicyAgreement regarding confidentiality.
IP addresses of users
ShareYourWallpaper can detect the IP address of your browser according to Internet-technology. This IP address is registered by our server especially for to help administer the website and track user's actions on the website. These details do not contain any personally identifiable information.
E-mail
Our server writes in the register of ShareYourWallpaper users’ e-mails only for their registration and calculation. ShareYourWallpaper will not lease, sell, or provide your personal information to any companies.
Sharing of Information
ShareYourWallpaper will only share information with 3rd parties if required to do so by law, or if by doing so we can protect the ShareYourWallpaper website and/or it's users. If you do not wish for others to know your personal details (for example - name and email address), it is recommended that you do not apply for membership.
Cookies use
ShareYourWallpaper uses cookies for the users’ comfort in order to save the browser settings and to help make each user's visit easier and more interactive. ShareYourWallpaper does not any methods for tracking users (the so-called “spy” or “1x1” gif images and so on).
Advertisements
Advertisements located on our website can be posted by a third party – advertisement firms. These companies can use the information regarding your visits on these or other web pages (your name, address, e-mail, and phone number are excluded) to place an advertisement of wares and services that might be interesting to you.
Links
ShareYourWallpaper links to several other websites and does not control the content of any outside websites and can not be held accountable for their content. We also are not in control of the privacy policies of these sites and recommend that all members carefully read the privacy policies of other websites that collect personally identifiable information.
Children under the Age of 13
As ShareYourWallpaper is a general-audience website, we can not allow children under the age of 13 to sign up for membership (in accordance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act). We ask that parents instead sign up for membership and monitor their children's activity on the website.
Changes to the Privacy Policy
If we make changes to this policy, we will let members know by posting mention of the changes on the homepage of this website. If we decide to use the personal details collected at membership signup (or during any other stage of a user's onsite activity) in any manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will let the user know via email. Users will be given a choice as to whether they want their information used in a different manner.
TOP UploadersTake a look at full TOP!Share|
Hottest Wallpapers» Sandra Bullock Photos» Charlotte Lewis Photos» Sandra Bullock Photos» Keeley Hazell Official Calendar» Drew Barrymore» Christina Hendricks» Monica Bellucci» Catherine Zeta Jones» Christina Aguilera in black latexBrowse» FAQ» Browse membersFriend Sites» Search & download files» Real Dating Site
Copyright © 2006 ShareYourWallpaper.com | Terms & Conditions | Privacy Policy | ContactsDisclaimer: We provide all content "as is", "with all faults" and without any warranty whatsover. We don't warrant any part of the content nor do we represent the content will meet your needs or that its operation will be uninterrupted or error free. The entire risk as to the quality and performance of the content is with you. Names of goods, names of companies, marks, trademarks, and symbols are trademarks of corresponding organizations.
